Guide to the Winterhouse Art and Design Collection of Ezra Winter
Yale University Arts Library
- Miscellaneous Research Materials, 1913-2010; Series III
  - "Edward Lawson" Shoebox
    - Design on the Land, 1971; Book (Box 11, Folder 155)
      Notes: p. 57 and 63 drawings by Lawson
    - Photocopies of Articles pertaining to Lawson, 1915-2010; Loose papers (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Picture Perfect Travels through the Litchfield Hills, 2003; Brochure (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Index Print, plus 4 negatives, October 29, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Landscapes in the Litchfield Hills ( New York Times ), August 31, 2003; Newspaper clipping (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Photo: Justice Stone (looks over a mural, Washington D.C., May 3, 1937), Photograph (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - Buildings and Building Management, January 5, 1925; Periodical (Box 11, Folder 161)
      Notes: pp. 29-34 only.